<!DOCTYPE document PUBLIC
        "-//Apache Software Foundation//DTD XDOC 1.0//EN"
        "http://maven.apache.org/dtd/xdoc_1_0.dtd">
<document>
    <properties>
        <title>My Java Docking Framework-Plaf : ToolWindowManager</title>
        <author email="adecaro@users.sourceforge.net">Angelo De Caro</author>
    </properties>

    <body>
        <section name="Introduction">
            <p>
                MyDoggy-Plaf contains the default implementation of mydoggy-api.<br/>
                Here you can found information about :
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <a href="./toolwindowManager.html">MyDoggyToolWindowManager</a> : the implementation of the ToolWindowManager interface.
                    That interface is the main entry point to manager MyDoggy. Using this interface
                    the user can register/unregister tool windows, groups. The user can get the
                    content manager instance and type descriptor templates.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <a href="./persistenceDelegate.html">XmlPersistenceDelegate</a> : the implementation of the PersistenceDelegate interface.
                    That interface provides useful methods to save and load the tool window manager's workspace.
                    When you request to save the workspace, all settings of ToolWindows with relative descriptors are saved.
                    To obtain an instance of PersistenceDelegate you have to invoke the method <code>getPersistenceDelegate</code>
                    of <code>ToolWindowManager</code> interface. So you can obtain a persistence delegate specific to a
                    particular tool window manager.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <a href="./contentManagerUI.html#MyDoggyTabbedContentManagerUI">MyDoggyTabbedContentManagerUI</a> :
                    the implementation of the TabbedContentManagerUI interface.
                    That interface represents a ui that use a component that lets the user switch between
                    a group of components by clicking on a tab with a given title and/or icon (i.e. JTabbedPane).
                </li>
                <li>
                    <a href="./contentManagerUI.html#MyDoggyDesktopContentManagerUI">MyDoggyDesktopContentManagerUI</a> :
                    the implementation of the DesktopContentManagerUI interface.
                    That interface represents a ui that use a container to create a multiple-document interface
                    or a virtual desktop.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <a href="./transparency.html">Transparency</a> : On Windows platform, starting from Windows 2000,
                    you can see the transparency in action for floating tool window and for detached contents. But
                    you can plug your own manager. See the relative page for an example that use JNA.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <a href="./resourceManager.html">Resource Manager</a> : The ResourceManager interface is used to
                    customize not only icons, colors and internationalization but also ui components creation,
                    with relative customization, and transparency manager.
                </li>
            </ul>
        </section>

    </body>
</document>
