<!DOCTYPE document PUBLIC
        "-//Apache Software Foundation//DTD XDOC 1.0//EN"
        "http://maven.apache.org/dtd/xdoc_1_0.dtd">
<document>
    <properties>
        <title>MyDoggy - My Java Docking Framework : ToolWindowManager</title>
        <author email="adecaro@users.sourceforge.net">Angelo De Caro</author>
    </properties>

    <body>
        <section name="Table of Contents">
            <ol type="1">
                <li>
                    <a href="#ToolWindowManager">What is a ToolWindowManager?
                    </a>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <a href="#ToolWindowManagerDescriptor">What is a ToolWindowManagerDescriptor?
                    </a>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <a href="#PersistenceDelegate">What is a PersistenceDelegate?
                    </a>
                </li>
            </ol>

        </section>

        <a name="ToolWindowManager"/>
        <section name="ToolWindowManager">
            <p>
                This interface is the main entry point to manage MyDoggy. Using this interface
                the user can register/unregister toolwindows, groups and so on.
                Furthermore, the user can obtain the content manager and type descriptor templates.
                <br/>
            </p>


            <p> ToolWindowManagerDescriptor
                This interface is used to modify the behaviours of the ToolWindowManager.
                <br/>
                You can now change the push-away mode of toolwindows and set corner components.
                See Using page for how to.
            </p>
        </section>

        <a name="PersistenceDelegate"/>
        <section name="PersistenceDelegate">
            <p>
                This interface provides useful methods to save and load the tool window manager's workspace.
                When you request to save the workspace, all settings of ToolWindows with relative descriptors are saved.
                To obtain an instance of PersistenceDelegate you have to invoke the method
                <code>getPersistenceDelegate</code>
                of
                <code>ToolWindowManager</code>
                interface. So you can obtain a persistence delegate specific to a
                particular tool window manager.
            </p>
            <p>
                When you request to save the workspace, all settings of toolwindows, and not only, with relative descriptors are saved.
                See the specific DTD, relative to the version of mydoggy that you are using, to know all information saved.
                <br/>

                To obtain the instance of the PersistenceDelegate for a specific ToolWindowManager use the following:
            </p>
            <source>PersistenceDelegate pstDelegate = twManager.getPersistenceDelegate();</source>

            <p>
                MyDoggy arrives with a default implementation provided by
                <br/>
                <code>org.noos.xing.mydoggy.plaf.persistence.xml.XMLPersistenceDelegate</code>
                <br/>
                This implementation use the xml format to store all necessary data.
            </p>
        </section>


    </body>
</document>
